Guide to the Central Washington University Faculty Papers, Martin R. Kaatz 1953-1993
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
- Graphic-Precipitation and Elevation, Seattle to Columbia River via Snoqualmie Pass (Box-folder 27-3)
- Maps -Ski Trails, 1987- (Box-folder 27-4)
- Maps-LT Murray recreation area (Box-folder 27-5)
- Notes- Columbia Basin, 1975-1999 (Box-folder 27-6)
- Photographs- Wenatchee National Forest, 1986- (Box-folder 27-7)
- Notes-Ireland, 1967- (Box-folder 27-8)
- Notes Urbanization and Farming Technology, 1966- (Box-folder 27-9)
- Manuscript- Vantage Ferry, 1919- (Box-folder 27-10)
- Photographs-Beverly Creek, 2004- (Box-folder 27-11)
- Photographs-Thorp Landslide, 1970- (Box-folder 27-12)
- Photographs-Thorp Landslide, 1970- (Box-folder 27-13)
- Newspaper Clippings-Drought Articles, 1977- (Box-folder 27-14)
- Notes-Lumber and Timber Data, 1993- (Box-folder 27-15)
- Newspaper Clippings-Oil Drilling in Kittitas County, 1981- (Box-folder 27-16)
- Publication-Timber Report, 1992- (Box-folder 27-17)
- Photographs and Negatives, Landslides, 1970-2004 (Box-folder 27-18)
- Maps and Correspondence, Tang Ranch Photographs-Slide, 1996- (Box-folder 28-1)
- Photographs-Slide, 1998- (Box-folder 28-2)
- Photographs –Satellite, 1974- (Box-folder 28-3)
- Aerial Photographs, Manastash Mounds, 1949- (Box-folder 28-4)
- Elevation Map and Notes, Kittitas County, 1992- (Box-folder 28-5)
- Maps and Lecture Note Missoula Floods (Box-folder 28-6)
- Map-Field Trip map #1, 1961- (Box-folder 28-7)
- Map -Table Mountain Road Elevation (Box-folder 28-8)
- Maps-Continental Glaciation (Box-folder 28-9)
- Map of Patterned Ground on Columbia Plateau (Box-folder 28-10)
- Photographs-Thorp Landslides, 1971- (Box-folder 28-11)
- Aerial Photographs- Swauk, 1986- (Box-folder 28-12)
- Maps from Thesis, THE BLACK SWAMP (extra copies), 1952- (Box-folder 28-13)
- Weather Radio cassette recordings related to Mt. St. Helens eruption, 1980- (Box-folder 28-14)
- Three microfilm articles in original shipping container: Waters and Flagler, Origin of Small Mounds of Columbia Plateau; Black, R. F., Permafrost a Review; Hay, Thomas, Stone Stripes, 1965- (Box-folder 28-15)
- Green Rubber Stamp: Martin Kaatz signature (Box-folder 28-16)
- Maps Ellensburg Boundary Floods, 2006-2009; Stored in Document Drawer 22 (Box-folder 29-1)
- Maps Ellensburg Zoning, 1997-; Stored in Document Drawer 22 (Box-folder 29-2)
- Aerial Photographs Missoula Floods, near Osoyos date unknown, Stored in Document Drawer 22 (Box-folder 29-3)
- Map Canada and Alaska, Stored in Document Drawer 22 (Box-folder 29-4)
- Maps Thesis The Black Swam originals, Stored in Document Drawer 22 (Box-folder 29-5)